hello Partners great to connect with you
I hope all of you are keeping fine and
are in good health it's indeed a
pleasure to connect with all of you
again
post pandemic Health has taken a
different meaning for all of us we have
have our own perspective in terms of how
to keep ourselves free also the old age
has become even truer the prevention is
better than cure for us it is utmost
important that we do what is required to
take care of what our customer needs you
have been our eyes and ears in terms of
ensuring that our customers are serviced
properly it's a great pleasure to
announce to you something very special
I'll come there in a bit but before I
get there we always have been talking
about and hearing from all of you that
you wanted a comprehensive solution
which takes care of prevention then
diagnostic consultation and if needed
cure most of the companies have always
focused on the last part which is cure
but here we've got something which will
take care of all four in every possible
aspect we have got Health Advantage Plus
we fit this combination of product is
unique in its own ways cashless this
takes care of everything that I spoke
about you want to take tele consultation
you want to do video consultation you
want to even take any other expert
advice this will take care of it we'll
do all that is required to keep fit and
I'm sure that each one of you will enjoy
what comes out when you discuss this
with your customers but I also like to
say that to supplement this further on
ground we have launched second phase of
hashtag unbelievable true the campaign
this campaign will be run across medium
I am very sure that you love it but more
than that we love getting your feedback
you will see us in every possible manner
whether it's TV in the digital site or
any other medium that you have an access
to I look forward to ensure that we make
a grand success of it we are there for
you in any possible manner that you need
look forward to your feedback let's make
the most of it thank you so much and all
the best
[Music]